https://www.japanimation.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to Content
Welcome to Japanimation!
Compare
/ WISHLIST / SUPPORT@JAPANIMATION.COM
Japanimation.com
Menu
T-ShirtsT-ShirtsHoodiesCosplayAction Figures PlushiesMerchandiseBags & BackpacksCell Phone AccessoriesCushions & PillowsHeadgearJewelryKeychainsMugsPinsPlaying CardsProp ReplicasTowelsTrading CardsWalletsWall ScrollsWristbandsMiscellaneousManga SuppliesComic Book PaperDrawing SuppliesHow-To BooksPens & MarkersSoftwareTool KitsDVD/CDDVDMusicNew ItemsSpecial DealsClearance T-ShirtsThe Vault
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Japanimation.com understands the importance of privacy and we are serious in taking care of the security and privacy of all personal information of our customers.
All personal information collected is used for processing orders and for customer service purposes in regards to fulfilling your order. When you order from Japanimation.com, you will be prompted to provide information including your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, and information relating to the method of payment such as your credit card number & expiration date.
Your e-mail address and/or phone number will be used to inform you of the status of your order or to contact you to resolve any issue regarding your order or account. Japanimation.com will not e-mail information unrelated to your order unless you have consented to joining our newsletter. Please contact us if you wish to be removed from our newsletter or received our newsletter erroneously.
All personal and payment information will be transmitted via a SSL encrypted secure server. Credit card information is only kept for processing your order.
Japanimation.com does not and will not sell, rent, exchange, transfer or distribute your personal information to third parties. The only exception for releasing information to third parties is in order to comply with the law.
Compare Products
Remove This Item
Compare
Clear All
You have no items to compare.
You have no items in your wish list.
About Japanimation
A unique place to find brand new, mint condition collectible action figures
that are no longer prodced and price much less compared to auction sites.
Contact
650-595-4663
contactus@japanimation.com
Our Address
990 Industrial Rd, Ste 101,
San Carlos CA 94070
©2020 Japanimation. All Rights Reserved.
About Us
Privacy
